[Music]
Well, hey, how's it going, folks? Hey,
hey, Dion. How are you? Yeah, really
good. Danny, how you doing? It's great
to be here, Dion Kypo. Great to join you
again. Yeah, nice. Yes. Well, I'm going
to I'm going to go off screen and let
you guys chat and be watching for for
questions so we can do Q&A later on.
Sounds good. Uh thanks, Dion. Uh Danny,
thanks a lot for sort of coming in. I
know we uh we kind of barged in on a on
a day of recordings. I think you've had
a whole bunch of them today on it. So,
we'll uh we'll test you out live here on
it. That works. I don't usually wear a
sport coat, but uh you know, just just
for you today, I wore a sport coat.
Yeah, you're doing it sort of wearing
the uh the formal wear. It's like I
guess if anybody knows anything about
me, it's like definitely sort of in the
in the uh Snick's original culture uh
not so much a suit sort of environment
on it, but uh I think as we sort of
barged into like protect enterprise
customers on it there like a little bit
of a show or serious uh lens to it that
uh that was great. Um so let me kind of
uh just introduce you a little bit. You
know people have kind of heard too much
about me uh on it but just talk a little
bit Danny about your background. Uh
Danny's uh I've had the pleasure of
knowing Danny. Oh wow. I'm sort of I
think a little bit embarrassed that now
it's like I think it's not quite 20
years but it's sort of starting to kind
of push that envelope on it. Uh uh as we
were building together some of the
original ABSSE products back in Sanctum
Watchfire uh and uh always uh sort of
was always at the cutting edge of sort
of understanding where we're building
out. Ended up uh continuing to lead some
uh uh research and security research at
IBM after it acquired uh Watchfire which
we worked at together. Um and then
through a bunch of sort of startup
journeys uh uh before sneak was CTO at
veh software talking also about sort of
a different type of risk right sort of
managing uh backup software uh in big
volume in the world of cloud which was
uh not always embracing we'll touch on
that a little bit security as as a first
principle uh on it and then uh lastly
you know we got the uh the chance to uh
draw you in to uh to Sneak to to come
and be sneak's CTO on it which is very
exciting So like a long uh amazing
history that I've had the pleasure of
sort of uh uh working with you at some
parts of it uh in the world of of risk
of security of it uh and today sort of
dive in a lot into AI. Um so uh did I
get any of that uh sort of uh wrong over
there uh Danny on it? Any key pieces you
want to add? No, that's 100% it. I
always like to remind people I started
as a pen tester actually doing security
testing, but I don't do very much of
that anymore. it uh it's been a fun
journey and and actually working with
you along alongside you over the years
has made it even better. So great to be
here.
Um so uh I guess we're going to go from
uh kind of go through a little bit the
maybe the unpleasant topic of uh hey you
can just sort of vibe code your way and
sort of have not carry some
consequences. We're going to try not to
be sort of too much sort of doom and
gloom, you know, because I think we're
both believers uh in it. Um and and
maybe maybe just to before we cap in, I
know you've been sort of delving into uh
AI today. You're sort of you know with a
security hat but also developer hat in
uh in Sneak. Uh do you want to say just
a couple of words about the type of AI
uh work uh that's been happening that
you've been immersed in before we get
into the subject matter?
Well, I always start the conversation
when people ask me about AI of what is
AI because I remember doing uh you know
cracking hash codes 20 years ago by
chaining up a whole bunch of FPGAAS and
so machine learning and and we've
evolved into where we are today. So I
usually like to start with that AI for
myself at least when I when I use the
term AI I tend to think of generative AI
which is more relatively newer in
nature. Um, but as you might expect,
we've been playing with all kinds of
generative AI here on the the sneak
side. Certainly, the one that comes up
the most is generating code, as I expect
most of the audience here is using some
kind of generative AI in in the code
world. Yeah. Yeah. Very much so. I uh I
recently heard uh just like a bit of a
snarky but still kind of true uh remark,
which is uh if it works, we call it ML.
If it doesn't work, we call it AI. which
was a which was kind of a little bit
funny like it's been around for a while.
Uh yes up the new frontier. Um so I
guess uh we we're going to cover a
little bit the security concerns of it
and I guess maybe just to tee that up as
as a question. So security is uh is a
real concern. AI is a very kind of
volatile world on it. uh and generally
the the the sense I get in conversations
is that often times security is a bit of
a blocker or at least a very kind of
source of anxiety uh when people are
embracing AI. So I guess my question to
you for starters is like what are you
seeing? Are you seeing security sort of
uh truly blocking organizations and
enterprises from embracing um uh AI into
the systems? uh is it you know are they
adopting it anyway or is it actually
slowing down? What are you seeing? Uh
we're definitely seeing them adopt it.
What I would say is unequivocally uh
people are moving forward with AI. If
you ask me kind of in the enterprise is
the customers of sneak it tends to be
you know certainly coding assistance we
see a lot of that but you also see a lot
of chat bots you see a lot of support
technologies and uh I would say well
over 80% of our customers are embracing
AI within the organization. Now if you
ask me the second question of what is
the biggest concern as they're doing
that it is security but I would say it's
not blocking things it's more of a
concern than a blocker in the adoption.
In fact adoption rates are extremely
high especially in the development
community. Yeah. And I'm curious like
are you feeling are the security people
you talk to, you know, they wish AI
wasn't adopted or are they also excited
to sort of have AI adopted? They're just
also afraid of the repercussions.
No, no, they're excited by it. The
developers I talked to all want to use
it. In fact, if the organization doesn't
allow it, I would say chances are better
than 50% for sure that they're using a
windsurf or, you know, a codium or a
cursor or a co-pilot or something within
their environment. So they're definitely
excited and and uh energized by it. The
one thing I would say is sometimes
they because this comment is now
everyone's a developer sometimes they
think well really like just because you
know how to talk to a prompt does that
make you a developer? So there is you
know there there's some cynicism there
but they're all adopting it. They're
embracing it is what I would say right.
Yeah. And I think um I guess one thing
I've uh I've been excited to sort of see
is that actually probably like many
people within the security organizations
are uh are like highly technical but not
good coders. Uh and in that sense I see
many of them actually kind of embracing
small tools uh the creation of small
tools with AI uh for their own systems.
Not like the way they would identify
attackers but just sort of integration
software or automation software of it.
um which I think is kind of fun sort of
to bring if you if you think hearken
back to the cloud if I use that analogy
you know in cloud um uh I think there
was probably more aversion or my sense
was there was more aversion about the
security teams they kind of preferred to
not use it and and here it sort of feels
like they're they're a little bit of a
user uh as well uh or an embracer I
don't know if you're sort of seeing that
in the world of appsec uh as well
yeah I'd say that's definitely the case
and and one of the areas is they're
using it for curiosity I unfortunately
began my career I guess back in Cobalt.
And so if you ask me what I'm most
familiar with, it's languages that are
older today are considered older C and
C++ and Cobalt and and those but and and
Python because I did a lot of security
testing but for example I will freely
admit I'm not very good at at Golang.
And so one of the ways I wanted to do
something in Go so you know I broke out
a coding assistant and I said hey can
you create this? And so what I'm seeing
in the development community is they're
using it to both augment skills in areas
that they may not have skills um but
they're using it to satiate the
curiosity of how do I use this in my
everyday life. Yeah. Cool. So I guess um
um when when people are u assessing a
security concern again I'm going to
probably like overdo the cloud analogy
over here in this conversation but uh um
you know when when the cloud came about
and it had a bunch of sort of security
uh uh concerns around it the the
solution was sometimes expected to come
from the cloud itself you know from the
platform itself and over time I guess we
sort of seen uh platforms like Sneak
platforms like for sort of cloud native
development or or like whiz or sort of
others for sort of CSPM and such
actually be the solutions that layer on
top of the cloud. So instead of it being
built in I guess how many do do you do
you have a sense of how do people feel
about uh hey the models will just become
secure or like know these these sort of
code generations they will kind of fix
it on their own versus a need for sort
of dedicated security solutions sort of
above above the fold.
Well, appsac people definitely believe
that it's not going to secure itself and
developers generally are more optimistic
and think that it will secure itself and
I I think that both are true. The
analogy to the beginning of of cloud
is actually super relevant because
if you think about the when the cloud
first started taking off, I mean it was
booming because people were saying hey I
can get our I can get footprint in an
area that I don't have. And if you fast
forward after the inception of cloud two
or three years, three big things were a
result of that. One is uh we're still
dealing with the security
misconfigurations of storage, right?
Open S3 buckets like no one was doing
anything about that. Then there was over
permissive AM and and access controls.
And thirdly, there was very poor
visibility and logging. And I would say
that those same three concepts apply
equally to AI. It's very much the same
and and security people who are aware of
this and know this say this is the era
that we're entering into. We're setting
ourselves up for failure if we don't
consider security going forward. Right.
Yeah. And they can anticipate that. And
of course some of the question is well
what can you do about it? Um and I think
I guess another uh topic we've had in uh
when when we think indeed about sort of
cloud and about application security is
this notion of like transcending
fragmentation right of uh if you're
using one model it might maybe you have
the aspiration that it will sort of
secure itself you know all those
concerns but when you're using kind of
multiple models you know do you do you
kind of expect each of them to just sort
of secure itself or do you need
something that's overarching I guess
when you're looking at enterprises today
are you are you seeing them generally
like you know pick a partner and kind of
go all in with them where you're sort of
seeing a breadth of tool and and kind of
model adoption.
Definitely a breadth of model and tool
adoption. Even I I'll use our
organization as an example. But we have
multiple coding assistants that are
being used here and we're using
multimodal things and we use you know
open AI for one thing we use claude 3.7
for another thing and and so that is
what I would say is typical and so if
you want governance across all the
different tools across all the different
models then you need something that is
outside of those
environments and while some models are
better than others at securing things I
would say there are zero models that can
secure everything and so having some
aware awareness of the types of
weaknesses I think is a pretty important
thing for most organizations to focus
on. So that's an excellent tea up
precisely to my next question which is
let's sort of get a little bit more sort
of technical. So like what are the
security concerns that people raise uh
the most as you as you sort of engage
with them and especially when it comes
to sort of AI development right and in
this world.
Well everyone starts with the OASP LLM
top 10. So you have model poisoning,
data training poisoning and prompt
injection and over permissive
permissions and all kinds of different
vulnerabilities that people are alluding
to. Um in in the context of coding, I
would say pause. Do you mind sort of
saying a little bit about the OS top 10
and the OS by 11 top 10 sort of the
developer audience doesn't necessarily
uh not everybody might know what those
are. Sure. Yeah. So, the Open Web
Application Security Project has always
had a top 10 of of vulnerabilities. And
uh in 2023, which two years ago was a
lifetime ago, but it was two years ago,
they published a top 10 vulnerability
list for LLMs. Um the first one of those
was Prompt Injection, and it went on
from there to model poisoning and data
theft and data exfiltration. And you can
you can Google it and find what those
top 10 are. I would say even in the two
years since that came to pass, I would
say those vulnerabilities tend to be out
of date because we're already facing new
vulnerabilities. When you have an agent
talking to an agent, there is no concept
of the vulnerabilities associated with
that. Um, so it's evolving and it's
evolving very quickly. So much so that
the standards bodies and and
organizations like OAS are it's it's
hard to keep up with those
vulnerabilities. Some of them though I
would argue guy are more real than
others. In other words, I think some are
overhyped but but some are more real and
they'll have longevity to them. So let's
dig into that. Maybe like you know a
couple of examples of like which ones do
you think maybe we'll start with the uh
the uh the real ones and then we'll sort
of talk a little bit about the ones
blown out of proportion. So like which
concerns do you find um maybe like if if
you named your own sort of top three uh
that someone we have an audience here of
developers or sort of building software
like which top three concerns them or
their organization should really kind of
uh focus on?
There are two that I personally worry
about a lot in the long term. One is
around identity and access management.
And the reason I say that is because
typically LLMs the large language models
are trained with all kinds of data. And
it's not true that everyone inside the
organization should have access to all
kind all of that data. And so you hear
this being used as jailbreaking the
system or getting data that you're not
supposed to have access to. That is
exacerbated tenfold when you have agents
talking to agents which we're beginning
to see now where you have some agent
using model context protocol to speak to
another agent and there's no concept of
passing on authorization. Obviously
authentication has been done but
authorization to the second model. So I
worry about that a lot in the concept of
code. Let me give you a specific example
of this. If if you have an LLM that has
all of your internal code libraries, you
may have code libraries for one group
that you don't want exposed to another
group. Well, how do you ensure that your
secondary agent, your coding assistant
knows that I can access this library set
but not this library set? How do you
pass that on? And so that's probably one
of my top concerns is around the data
access. Um, right. The second thing is
the non-deterministic nature. As a
security person, I'm always kind of very
linear in thinking of if I put in this
particular, you know, payload, I can
exploit the system and do get it to do
something that I I don't want it to do.
By their very definition, AI and code
generation of AI is non-deterministic.
And so having an audit trail and being
able to meet compliance requirements is
actually really difficult in a world of
AI. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. very interesting
kind of the uh the notion of attacks. I
wonder if it's like a new pattern of
attackers in which like uh you know if
it uh if you don't like the weather wait
you know wait five minutes uh type
element was like hey if you're like if
this signal injection didn't work just
try it again in five minutes on it maybe
a new version of AI came along and maybe
that one is vulnerable. Um, yeah. And
that manifests itself in different ways
because if you're doing red teaming,
like if you're doing sequential prompt
injection, you might do the exact same
sequential prompt injection a second
time and it works and the first time it
didn't just simply because of the
non-deterministic nature. So that could
give you an inflated sense of of
confidence and and that's that's a
problem in a deterministic security
world. Yeah. Yeah. Absolutely. because
you can't really attest to to anything
having kind of some some longevity uh to
it. And how um I I guess how are people
uh dealing sort of let's sort of focus
on those two. I guess the first one is I
think more of a constraint right I I
very much relate to like identity access
and uh or you know instead of me sort of
narrowing it down let's talk a little
bit about those two cases and maybe what
are some sort of mitigating uh controls
or what can someone do except for don't
use uh uh don't use AI right or don't
use
well I never recommend that I'm a big
believer in embracing it but on the the
authorization authentication mostly
authorization less authentication
um side we're beginning to see it worked
into some of the underlying frameworks.
So you're beginning to see extensions of
MCP model context protocol to have
authorization in there. And in fact,
we're a member of the consortium for
secure AI. And so you're beginning to
see these frameworks, the A to A
framework is another one. Google
announced that at Google next a month
ago or so and at the time didn't have
any authorization in it, but already the
working groups are coming together and
saying, "Hey, let's introduce it." So my
hope is and Microsoft has embraced that.
So now you have two giants both
embracing the same concept. So my belief
is that in the longer term um we'll
start to work in authorization and
identity and access management into the
systems. Um the nondeterministic natur
is like uh you wait for the industry
standards to to firm up. You participate
in them if you are uh you know like if
you care enough and are able to do so.
Um and I guess in the meantime you sort
of avoid topics that require them
because they're just not satisfied quite
yet.
Yeah, I would be very hesitant to do a
lot around agentto agent communication
or agentic to agentic systems because of
that. Give it six months, give it a year
and I think we're okay. That's not to
say don't embrace AI right now. I just
be more cautious when you can get into
the meta layer of of talking across
systems. Yeah. And I think that's okay
like riskreward should always be kind of
uh uh assessed on it. And I guess on the
on the second problem of dynamic code
and the code kind of constantly
changing first of all like I think I
think that probably relies like it's
especially true for agentic systems that
might sort of change the code a bit more
uh dramatically shall we say. So before
let me kind of do a bit of a side
tangent. We come back to this risk like
I guess uh how much do you see agentic
uh kind of full-on you know Devon style
sort of agentic systems being used uh in
enterprises like are there still in like
a oh this is really cool I want to kind
of try it out in the corner or are you
sort of seeing any sort of um real
adoption on it on enterprise systems?
What I've seen and this is the segment
of the customers maybe that we're
dealing with. What I've seen is uh this
is cool let me try it out on the corner.
I kind of grouped them into three
buckets, guy. I have the the highly
agentic autonomous ones like Devon. You
have kind of the medium ones like
augment that, you know, can do a lot of
things, but they're not fully
autonomous. And then you have the more
of the assistant, you know, the the
cursor co-pilot type style. I'd say very
few customers within our customer base
at least are going to the fully agentic.
Um, I would say most of them are
actually in that lower autonomous model
with the co-pilots and cursors and maybe
20-ish percent 30-ish percent are in
kind of the middle that are doing very
much more augmented uh code. Yeah.
Assistance. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
Interesting. So I guess kind of coming
back to the sort of dynamic nature of it
or sort of you know like how do you deal
with compliance I guess uh you know how
do you how do you kind of pass that uh I
guess what what are there any any kind
of innovative uh approaches that you're
sort of seeing like how are people
dealing with that
well a lot of logging in visibility I
said in the early days of the cloud that
had these three problems and the third
one was that there wasn't a lot of
logging in visibility and the good news
is people are logging it and actually
getting interesting metrics out of I I
met with a large financial institution,
a customer of ours that said 11% of our
code is AI generated. And I kind of
scratched my head and I said, "How do
you get to 11%." But what they were
doing was they were logging all the code
that was being submitted into their
source control management systems and
then they were logging all the code that
was being generated and they were doing
some simple mathematics and division on
that. So, you know, whether that's
accurate or not, for me, the positive
outcome is that they were logging it.
They were actually tracking it. Um and I
think we'll see more of that as as we go
forward. Yeah. Yeah. Makes sense. I
guess maybe let's do some uh some myth
busting you know uh of it. So I guess
which uh which security concern or two
do you feel uh is is you know you can
theorize about it but it's slightly
blown out of proportion.
I tend to think the hallucinations is
pretty blown out of proportion. I'm not
saying it doesn't happen. I just think
that over time we're going to see fewer
hallucinations. And the reason why we'll
see that is mostly because the models
will will test themselves before it
returns output. And so I think um
hallucinations would be one of them.
Identity and access management I think
will get out of that problem over time.
I think data theft is a very low I'm not
saying it's not real. It's definitely
real. But if you ask me to rate it on a
risk uh category, I think the likelihood
of that being exploited is is very low.
And so, you know, I always measure
things on a risk scale as opposed to a
an actual security scale. And so, while
some of these things are real, I just I
think they're lower risk than other
areas, right? Yeah. And they might be
sort of short-term risk. And I guess
which which um when you think about, you
know, fundamentals like I guess you you
in general when you think about sort of
Genai and these tools, you know, some
flaws are are just, you know, the baby
steps, right? It's just immature yet.
It's sort of evolving so rapidly. uh and
some are maybe a bit more fundamental.
Um I guess which which security concern
or two do you feel kind of have legs
here and they're going to sort of stay
they'll they'll hurt us for a while or
they'll just be a concern that we really
need to uh uh to fundamentally sort of
consider because it's going to it's
going to be here. I I would go back to
the same three things that I said about
the cloud and that's because we don't
learn our lessons. In other words, I
think that the configuration of of AI is
is a problem and will be continue to be
a problem generally around the
permissive nature and what data it's
trained on and all of that. The second
thing being over permissive uh identity
access management to the data where
we're giving customers access to let's
say I'm training an LLM and I put all of
my support data in there. Do I really
want to do that if I'm giving customers
access to it because they could break
out of their set of data? So, I think
that's the second one. And then uh the
third one I would go back to the
visibility and logging. I think we're
going to fall into the same trap that we
did before that we're not uh doing
sufficient visibility and logging and we
we end up in the same place we were with
cloud after two or three years. Yeah. Of
not knowing not knowing what is where
and and how is it happening. And I guess
the the the other lens I I I think
sometimes about uh some some security
concerns are uh due to the nature of the
new technology and others are um uh
they're they're just they're just a an
amplification of patterns that we've
already seen before, right? So like
cloud accelerated development or like
DevOps accelerate but like agile came
before that and you know in you know
over time like just sort of things moved
at a faster and faster pace. Um uh and
you know similarly maybe like uh ease of
creation improves and as ease of
creation uh improves like responsible
like the level of scrutiny or maybe the
level of proficiency or uh
professionalism uh involved in watching
these things that goes and that's true
also like when I create images like I I
create images in a very non-professional
way and that's okay. I'm not going to
like uh build any sort of a business
around my kind of AI image creation I
guess. Do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do you think does that
distinction work for you and and if you
had to choose like which which path you
think is scarier you know you're it
sounds like you're sort of maybe leaning
more towards the how we use it versus
the tech but I don't know if I'm
well I'm a big believer in that we
should use it like I I am not a slow
down at all we should use AI embrace AI
I guess my I always fundamentally go
back to we need to build in security
from the very beginning the problem that
we've historically fallen into Every
time we embrace a new infrastructure,
doesn't matter whether it's cloud or
servers or virtualization or AI, we we
forget the fundamentals which are
validate your input and code your
output, apply identity and access
control management. Like it it's funny
while the threats are or the attacks are
somewhat different because the
infrastructure is different. The root
causes for them guy are it's been the
same for 20 years. I mean write shield
we were testing the input that was going
to an application, right?
Yeah. Yeah, a lot of the sort of the
same uh fundamentals. I do find for what
it's worth that the I find myself almost
more concerned about the explosion of uh
of uh of usage uh than uh than maybe
even the fundamentals of it which are
much more sort of interesting but uh uh
we've kind of seen how security hygiene
is the uh is eventually the things that
organizations actually get breached like
yeah what is different today than 20
years ago is there's far more data
behind these systems so the risk risk is
greater if compromise occurs. 20 years
ago there wasn't the same amount of data
and now all of the data is behind there
and if the wrong person gets access to
it that can be very detrimental.
Excellent. Uh we have time flies here.
We sort of have five more minutes. I've
got a few more questions to you and then
we have some time for Q&A. So I just
wanted to remind everybody that you can
post questions in the comments and we'll
have a few minutes for Q&A uh uh in a
few minutes on it. Um I guess uh uh
we're going to try and kind of go
dystopian utopian over here a little
bit. So like we called this talk the age
of risky software. Um let's talk a
little bit about like what is what is
the concern here? What is the uh um you
know the path we need to be beware or or
or is there even one right is sort of a
is it set to fall like what what do we
mean by that? The age of risky software
the in the early inception days of the
new technology change is always the
riskiest because the pressure on the
business and I'm sure this is true of
everyone in the audience is use AI use
AI be more productive go fast go fast go
fast and so the the early days are are
the greatest risk and we are in the
early days of AI we don't understand it
I was listening to a podcast this
weekend of if you said Dave and Busters
in a in a voice message the voice
message never got delivered on an iPhone
still True. By the way, today if you so
persona type words that
are
mysteriously Yeah. And we don't
understand how the AI is working
sometimes. And so we're in this age of
risky software because we're in this go
fast, go fast, go fast without truly
understanding how it's working, how to
secure it, doing all the right things.
And so we're in the age of risky
software. Yeah. Yeah. I think that makes
sense. I do wonder maybe coming back to
sort of the uh overused sort of cloud
analogy we've been doing here is when
you think about the adoption of the
cloud you know the the initial adoption
was similar like just as you're saying
you know like pressure to adopt uh
people used it and it kind of there was
sort of this like world of possibilities
and we kind of went from a place like we
forget this but like infrastructure used
to be a fairly secure thing you know
like people like the servers and all of
that they were sort of run by a fairly
small very professional typically very
security aware
group that was moving way too slow,
which is the reason for the drive. And
then cloud kind of opened it up and
suddenly people could do it faster and
more people could do it and oftentimes
without any really understanding of what
it is that they're performing. And you
know fast forward not that many years
after uh and until today as you point
out like misconfigurations and sort of
flaws uh in uh in in in sort of
infrastructure and cloud infrastructure
typically are such a massive maybe the
top uh cause for uh for breaches. And I
guess I wonder as we as we
enable everyone to be a creator, which I
love, you know, like as a that notion
that to be a developer of sorts of a
type of developer, like a creator of
software um along lines alongside
allowing existing developers to sort of
run at like a much much faster speed
with a bit less uh kind of scrutiny on
it. uh like our vulnerabilities in code
the the the equivalent are they going to
be sort of our our achilles heel later
and I don't know like does that resonate
is that a conversation I guess that uh
and and are we doomed to sort of just
accept it if it is because it is what it
is that tech will be adopted I'm an
optimist I believe in the long run it
this will sort itself out but you know
you've titled this the age of risky
software and I think that's why that is
the case like what we're doing is
democratizing coding
uh clearly um and so we're going fast
and we're opening up the aperture
similar to the what the cloud did to
more and more people and so the result
is more code and more code means more
vulnerabilities right now over time I
think we'll start to implement the
controls and the guardrails to to secure
that um and I also don't that's why
you're still going to have developers
just because more people can do
development that doesn't eliminate the
need for developers my son's actually in
computer science and he said dad should
I be worried about you there there not
being a need for developers in the
future. And I say that's ridiculous. Of
course, there's going to need to be
developers. What we're really doing is
opening the aperture to to more
development. And when we do that, what
we need are the security guard rails in
place to ensure that we don't end up in
a similar position the cloud ended up
in. Right. Right. Yep. Just try to
anticipate. Um, hey Danny, I'm going to
switch to a bunch of questions. We
actually Oh, here Dion kind of Yes,
indeed. Uh I think I learned sort of the
operate the system and I found them. Uh
Dion over here.
So uh um uh maybe I'll just sort of lean
in here and sort of ask ask Dan these.
So uh Michael Wolf asks uh uh you made a
comment on passing authorization
authentication around when agents uh uh
uh uh talk to agents. That sounds
parallel to passing around ownership and
trading value for intellectual property
or microp payments. Do you see security
and ownership sort of in a similar lens?
I guess this is to me more about like
what what are the sort of the the assets
and the validity of them that are moving
around.
I I see the problem is similar but I see
them as very distinct problems. The
ownership of intellectual property and
with AI is a real issue and I don't want
to minimize it. That's true for music.
It's true for art. It's true for code.
It's true for language and books and all
of this. I can I can go tell AI to write
me a book. Well, who should get paid on
that? I I I'm not sure the answer to
that. I think there is a secondary issue
that is similar but a different problem
that has to do with should they get
access to that music, art, you know,
text, code, whatever it happens to be.
So parallel but distinct. The the reason
why the microp payments is important is
if we want the proliferation of AI to
continue, then there needs to be some
model of attribution because otherwise
you're going to lose all the people that
are contributing data into the LLMs or
the diffusion models that are behind AI.
Yeah. Yeah. No, I think uh I think well
said on it and it's interesting to also
think a little bit about the uh data
assets that get moved around with uh
protection on top of them. So that's
also interesting. In that case maybe
they do blend a little bit more as I
almost like DRM style like you pass
along content with some uh security
aspects to it. Um I guess another
question is uh how uh how will the role
of uh attestation play uh play out in
terms of sort of AI agents and sort of a
supply chain like when you think about
creation with AI and such Jason asked
this you have a view here's one where I
yeah I I actually think the government
we're going to see compliance step in
and usually I'm not a big fan of uh of
regulation of of new technologies
because it's very difficult especially
for startup helps to deal with it. But I
think because of current compliance
requirements, if you look at PCIDSS or
any of these, you know, regulations or
compliance requirements, they require
validation of certain things. And so
that is going to require attestation of
AI native software that is backed by
LLMs and I think this is going to solve
itself. My only worry and concern guy is
that it becomes very fragmented. What
you don't want is a GDPR for every
country in the world or every state in
the United States. and like that's a bad
position to be in. So hopefully we
consolidate around some very common
wellthoughtout uh requirements or
regulations around attestation. Yeah.
Yeah, that makes sense. But and also
makes sense kind of at the meta level
which is AI will be unpredictable but
there's no reason for it not to be
traceable. You might not know what will
happen but you want to do that. I think
I've got two more questions. I think we
really kind of have time for one. Uh so
one was about the scope of AI security.
I'm going to pass on that. Uh sorry
about that. It's just I think it's sort
of too big for the time that we have uh
to capture here. Alexa maybe something a
bit more concrete which is which
security checks uh can developers
currently build into their agents to try
and mitigate as many risks as possible.
Kind of ending on a very practical bit
of advice.
Yeah. Well, I would say two things. One
is if you're using open source
components and actually one of the
things that worries me about AI coding
assistance by the way is that it
replaces to some extent open source
components and tries to custom create
them because what's the downstream
patching and updating of all those open
source components. That's a problem. Um
but I would say two things. One is
validate the packages that you're
pulling in uh for for validation and
then code that you're writing. It's very
easy. You can use AI actually to test
the data flow across that code and to
generate a fix for it. And so if you ask
me very practically, what I think you
should do is validate your open source
packages and if you're writing custom
code, validate that the flow of that
code isn't breaking the build in other
areas. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I love that.
And uh and I guess, you know, the more
you automate that, the faster you can
run, right? And people kind of forget
that putting guardrails, you know, it
sounds like a a cumbersome thing, but
actually when you put the guardrails in,
when you're sort of running on a bridge
with rails, you can run faster because
you're not afraid to fall. And uh so we
we want to put those in. Um yeah, time
flies. We're sort of uh here we are sort
of uh 35 minutes sort of uh later on.
And Danny, uh huge thanks again for
coming in and sharing this knowledge and
for uh I guess investing in uh in AI
security.
Well, thank you for having me guy. It's
a great conversation. Very cool. Uh and
uh Dion, I think we are ready for our
sort of next session. I don't know if
you want to sneak in one sort of final
question for us. Uh but uh yes, I know
there are a few more that were that were
in there. I'm really curious about just
developer trust, you know, like as
developers use all of these tools like
how how do they get a feel for what they
can and cannot trust? Uh it seems like
there's a lot of perception and feel
which is interesting. That's feels good
there. Yeah. Thanks so much for for the
chat and uh really appreciate it. We're
gonna move on to the next one. Thank
you, Danny. Thank you, Guy.